has taken over. What makes him someone
ready for this job, do you think?
>> Oh, yeah, man. First off, I mean, it's
good to be back. You know, it's a
blessing to be back. Always. Uh, don't
never take it for granted. And talking
about State, man, he just even last
year, I just he came in every day,
grinded, uh, brought great energy to the
room, uh, was always locked in on the
details. And so, I'm looking forward to
working with him. You know, I got a good
relationship with him. And I know he's
looking forward to it. I bought in. I've
already talked to him a little bit
about, you know, the new offense and a
little bit of details about that. So,
just uh a lot of details coming from him
and I know he's going to be great to
work with.
>> What What jumped out at you with working
with him last year, last couple years,
like what what jumped out to you about
him just as a coach?
>> His attention to detail. You know, he
was just a guy that I could always go
to. um I could pull him to the side and
you know ask him for greater details
whether it's scheme technique and you
know as a former player it's just having
a guy like that that you can talk to
that's that's been in your seat been in
your seat been in your shoes understands
the ins and outs of the game is always
good to be able to have a guy like that
to talk to
>> thank you
>> hi Trent um just with David Blau um
could you notice any signs over the last
couple years that he might be a good
coordinator for the future good play
calling for the future.
>> Yeah, I mean talking about Blau just
talk about a dude that always showed up
and you could just see him always
another guy just locked in and every
week um he had some part in the game
plan. You know, I think a lot of times
he would be able to put in some play or
just have some type of input on the
offense and he was very passionate about
it and you know he would I could see his
relationship with Jaden and how he
worked with those guys and so it's a guy
that I know that's been putting in the
work. you could always see that he had
the potential to be, you know, a very
good coach in this league and a young,
bright, energetic mind. And so, I'm glad
he got the opportunity. I know he's
going to take advantage of it.
>> Have you already started lobbying to
catch a few passes in the red zone or
>> I haven't yet, but I mean, hey, I'm all
I'm all for putting that back in. Let's
doing it again.
>> Donna,
>> hey Tan, welcome back again. Uh, talk
about the the offensive line a little
bit more. uh you know some of the moving
parts uh coach Blau talked about
emphasis we we put when we talked to him
early on the running game. Could you
just talk a little bit about that and
the offensive line right now as you see
it?
>> Uh I just I think we had a great room,
you know, starting with, you know,
talking about guys like LT and having
one of the best left tackles in the
league in the room and being able to
pick his brain on a daily basis. Um
that's invaluable to, you know, the
younger guys in the room and even guys
like me. So that's just that's huge. And
everybody else, I mean, everybody, we
have a lot of guys with a lot of
experience in our room. A lot of it's a
unique room. You talk about guys that
have won Super Bowl champions and WY and
U Nick Aliggrady. And so, you know, it's
just a collection of guys who are, you
know, hardworking and really bought in
to the room as a whole. And um no
individual basis, everybody's just, you
know, trying to make the room better as
a unit. And so I think when everybody
buys in like that, you know, you usually
have a good room.
>> And and and looking at your yourself,
you've been a staple here. They they
signed you back again. How do you see
yourself this year in in this offense
and moving forward?
>> Like like every season for me, I'm here
to compete. Um obviously everybody in
this league wants to play and I want to
get on the field and play and contribute
to this team and, you know, help us, you
know, win. That's that's my ultimate
goal every year. And so I'm just here
to, you know, be a good room guy and
help everybody get better in every way
that I can and push everybody in every
way I can and show up and be consistent
and, uh, like I said, any way that I can
offer help to anybody in the room. But,
you know, ultimately, I just want to be
a competitor in the room and help that
to rub off on everybody else and give us
our best chance at winning.
>> Good to see you again.
>> You, too,
>> Ben.
>> Hey, Trent. Um, obviously you don't have
to be a former player to be an offensive
line coach, but is there something
different when you're working now with
somebody who did play the position, um,
as opposed to somebody who didn't?
>> Absolutely. I think when you talking
about, excuse me, when you're talking
about, you know, how a guy sees
something on film or, you know, I can
talk, it's just the language sometimes
and and even just like I said, just
being in in those shoes and
understanding, you know, the angles in
which I'm coming from when I ask a
question. And so, I think just that
experience is invaluable. And um we
actually
so our look team for the week if you're
not playing we would have meetings with
state on the um Friday or Saturday
before our practice and we will watch
that tape because you know that's how
important it was to us as a unit as
getting better even when you're not
playing. So um I think that just speaks
to him as a leader in the room and
helping you know being invested in
everybody getting better. So him as a
player, I think he understands that
because he went through the same thing.
He experienced the same thing in his
room.
>> And um you know, we've seen you play
tackle, we've seen you play guard, sort
of joking, but any chance you play
center because I think that's spot right
now that's up a little bit up in the
air.
>> Yeah, I've never um actually played
center um at this level. Um I've done it
before, but you know, I'm a guy that,
like I said, I just want to help the
team and help the room be better. So,
you know, anything that's asked of me at
this point, you know, I'm willing to do.
Um, I don't shy away from that. I mostly
play tackle and guard, but um, like I
said, anything that's asked of me, I'll
be willing to do.
>> Thanks. Congrats.
>> Thank you,
>> Candy.
>> Hey, Trent. Welcome back and
congratulations. Thank you.
>> Um, kind of piggybacking on Donna's
question. So, for this off season, what
are you working on and what are kind of
your areas of focus for yourself? uh
areas of focus for me in the offseason
always just getting my body back from
the season and you know improving in
that way first. You know, shaking off
the rust there and improving mobility,
getting my body comp together and then
you know strengthwise and technique-wise
always just looking over the things last
year that um maybe areas that I need to
improve on and areas that I do well
strengthening those and you know you
just take those and 1% better try to get
better every day. You know, you stack
those days, stack those weeks, and then
you go into the offseason program and
you get back with the guys and you
compete and like I said, you learn from
learn more from guys like LT and the
coaching staff and you just keep putting
your best foot forward and every year
you try to show up and be a better
version of yourself.
>> And you have now mentioned him a couple
of times, um, Larry Mutansel. What are
some of the things? Can you give some
examples of what you have learned from
him so far?
>> Yeah, I do. I mean, uh, you know, I do I
look up to the guy cuz I I appreciate
how he goes about his business. You
know, you talk about a guy who, um, very
routine guy, very, you know, shows up to
practice, goes through the same type of
routine, and it shows up in his play.
Um, very consistent with his, um,
technique, with his knowledge of the
game. And so, like I said, me being a
guy, I have appreciation for the game.
And so, I do I look up to that and I um,
you know, I kind of want to model a lot
of my ways around that. So, um, yeah, I
mean, it's huge.
>> Thank you so much and congratulations
again.
>> Thank you,
>> Blake.
>> Welcome back, Trent.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Now, you spoke it into existence, right?
>> Yes, sir. We did.
>> All right. So, you know, when when you
look at, you know, you're coming back
and you look at some of the other moves
that have been made, you know, this team
looks like it could be in a good
position to compete again at the highest
level. Uh, but look at some of the uh
moves that have been made on offense,
you know, how exciting does that make
you as a a guy that's going to be
blocking for Rashad White now and some
of the other pieces?
>> Oh, super exciting, man. I mean, you
talk about a group and we spoke about
it, man. This wasn't a team who was, you
know, we went through our struggles last
year, but this wasn't a team that was
laying down, you know, any week. Every
week we um prepared and competed our
butts off to try to go out there and get
a win. And you know, sometimes it didn't
work out. But I, you know, I can tell
you this, the guys that are in this
locker room, returning to this locker
room, and I'm sure the guys that are new
um are looking forward to turning that
around and, you know, just coming back
and putting in the work. And so, it is
exciting. You know, when you got a uh a
guy like Jaden Daniels and a lot of
these pieces that are around him, it's
just it's exciting as a offense. And
then you add a guy like David Blau that,
you know, like I said, going to bring
that young energy and um great mind. And
so I'm looking forward to it.
>> And then also I just wanted to ask you
as far as you know kind of uh you know
go off of what Candy had mentioned
before as far as your off season. You
know we've talked about some things that
you do training wise but is it something
you want to do where you come back in
bigger or or lighter or anything like
that?
>> Not necessarily. Um I'm usually around
the same I guess weight my playing
weight or whatever. So, like I said,
it's more like a recomposition thing
from the season and, you know, to break
it down to the base form is just, you
know, gaining muscle and losing fat, you
know. So, comes to that and putting on
strength and sometimes that comes with
like a change in weight, but nothing too
crazy. So, I'm usually around, you know,
15, 315 around there. Yep. Okay.
>> All right, man. Good seeing you,
brother.
>> Yes, sir. You, too.
>> All right. Appreciate it, Trent. Thanks.
>> Appreciate y'all.